do think media is
obviously a critical ecosystem
player It does keep
checks and balances Our
job more than maybe
the founder's job maybe
the founder's job is
not to vent but
also figure out how
to build their leverage
But our job is
to kind of some
of these things and
call out things that
actually everybody in the
ecosystem knows is happening
I don't know how
did you feel about
Glass Wall last year
Yeah fantastic Like was
truth seeking exercise right
We every single bit
and then I took
my team together and
I say hey look
there's a of Let's
just imagine because we
don't know who are
let's imagine ourselves saying
sorry to them if
they were you know
this is like exercise
ho no po no
like you can Google
it nobody can probably
spell it But you
go to like you
visualize a is suffering
and you go like
I'm sorry I love
you please forgive me
thank you right And
you just repeat that
it's not I you
can think that you
healing somebody But you're
actually trying to create
like a conversation of
because clearly like any
and every VC had
their missteps along the
way Every VC who's
born in this ecosystem
has a bad meeting
or whatever Yeah everyone's
got a bad day
and it's on both
sides and people have
bad days and worse
you So I feel
like what I always
want my team members
to do is to
just take ownership as
a